[{
    "questionNumber": 1,
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "BOKBYTAREN",
    "correctAnswer": "Kobe Bryant",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },{
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "JETENS YROR",
    "correctAnswer": "Terry Jones",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },{
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "GUDALIK SORK",
    "correctAnswer": "Kirk Douglas",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "OLLE LAGMAN",
    "correctAnswer": "Ola Magnell",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },{
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "BROUGH TEFLON",
    "correctAnswer": "Olof Thunberg",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "BRAKA INOMHUS",
    "correctAnswer": "Hosni Mubarak",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "SNOWY VAX MOD",
    "correctAnswer": "Max von Sydow",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "EKORRENS GNY",
    "correctAnswer": "Kenny Rogers",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "SANDIG LAMA",
    "correctAnswer": "Adam Alsing",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "HERR DILLCITAT",
    "correctAnswer": "Little Richard",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "HORNET NI KNEP",
    "correctAnswer": "Henrik Pont√©n",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "LO I HAMN",
    "correctAnswer": "Ian Holm",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "ORON I CEREMONIN",
    "correctAnswer": "Ennio Morricone",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "NIO HALVVILDA IDEAL",
    "correctAnswer": "Olivia de Havilland",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "COMBINED HACKSAW",
    "correctAnswer": "Chadwick Boseman",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "BRIS HUNGRAR BUDGET",
    "correctAnswer": "Ruth Bader Ginsburg",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "DE HADE INAVEL",
    "correctAnswer": "Eddie Van Halen",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "ANNOY SCREEN",
    "correctAnswer": "Sean Connery",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "VENT OR SWELL",
    "correctAnswer": "Sven Wollter",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "NIAGARA DOOMED",
    "correctAnswer": "Diego Maradona",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": "",
    "questionType" : "BUZZ_RUSH",
    "questionText": "JARL OCH NERE",
    "correctAnswer": "John le Carre",
    "questionScore": 2,
    "questionClues" : [{
      "clueScore" : 0,
      "clueText" : ""
    }]
  }
]

